Register to the Papers of Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
Yale University Music Library
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1890-1991; Series I; 32 boxes (13.3')
  - CORRESPONDENCE - Personal, I.A
    - DiPiazza, Joseph, 1986 Aug. 4; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - d'Istria à Olmeto, Michelle, 1965 June 10; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dohnanyi, Klaus von, 1982 June-July; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dokovska, Paulina, 1978-1979; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dolger, Manolita, 1965 May 13; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dom Musei P. I. Chaikovskogo v Klinu, 1945 June; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dooley, Pal, 1989 Nov. 12; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dorfmann, Ania, 1976-1978; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Dormann, Henry O., 1978 Mar. 27; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
      First p. missing
    - Dotson, Lee, ca. Jan. 1988; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Downes, Olin, 1947-1959; 15 items. (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Downes, Mrs. Olin, 1966-1968; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Drusin, Ronald E., M.D., n.y. Nov. 27; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Dubal, David, 1980-1991; 19 items. (Box 4, Folder 61)
      See also: I. B. - Literary requests
    - Dubinin, Yuri V. and Mrs. Yuri V., 1988-1989; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Dudman, Richard, 1978 Feb. 27; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Dugan, Marion (Mrs. Charles W.J.), 1969 Jan.-Feb.; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Dukakis for President Committee, ca. 1988 Oct. 10; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Duluth Ballet, 1989 May 10; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Dumm, Robert W., 1988 Feb.-Oct.; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Dunker, Lena, ca. 1986 Apr.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 62)
      Program from Vladimir Horowitz's 1926 Jan. 10 Hamburg recital laid in
    - D'Urso, Mario, 198-? Oct. 9; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Duteurthe, Marion, 1989 Jun. 10; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Dyszel, Bill, 1986-1987; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Eberhardt, Andrew, 1988 Sep.-Oct.; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 63)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz reply and an enclosure
    - Eckhard, Ulrich (Box 4, Folder 63)
      See: Berliner Festspiele
    - Economu, Maria, 1985-1989; 5 items. (Box 4, Folder 63)
      See also: Lopes, Giuliana
    - Edel'man, Georgii, 1962 July 2; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Edgar M. Leventritt Foundation, Inc.
    - Educational Testing Service, 1968-1969; 10 items. (Box 4, Folder 63)
      Includes 7 enclosures
    - Ehrenberg, Otto, 1965-1967; 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Eiges, O. (Oleg) [Konstantinovich], n.d.; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Eindhoven Druk B.V., 1987 Nov. 9-23; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Eisenhower, Susan, 1987 June-July; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Eisenhower World Affairs Institute
      See: Shultz, George
    - Eissler, K.R., M.D., 1965 Mar.-Apr.; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Eitington, Bess, 1965 May 10-24; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Elder, Dean M. (Box 4, Folder 64)
      See: Clavier
    - Elkan, Wolf, M.D., 1990 May 30; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Elmer, William B., 1984 Feb.-May; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Elton, Francesca, 1989 Nov. 18; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Emerson, Michael
      See: London Artists
    - Emerson Quartet
      See: Finckel, David
    - Englander, Roger, 1965 Apr.-May; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
      Includes Wanda Horowitz and Vladimir Horowitz reply
    - English, Henry Haines Perry, 1976-1978; 8 items. (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Ernst, E. Peter, 1986 Aug. 4; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 65)
      3 enclosures
    - Eschenbach, Christoph, 1988 Apr.-June; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Escobar, Sergio, 1990 Jan. 10; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Esquire (periodical), 1968 Mar.5; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Etude (periodical), 1949-1950; 3 items. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Evans, Allan, 1989 Mar. 6; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Evidon, Richard, 1991 Sep.-Oct.; 2 items. (Box 4, Folder 65)
      Includes Wanda Toscanini Horowitz reply
    - Express Private Car & Limousine Service Inc., ca. 1988 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Fairfield University, 1970 Jan.-Feb.; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Famely, Lena, 1986 Sep. 30; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Fanfani, MariaPia, 1989 Nov. 13; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Fantacci, Penelope March, 1989 Nov. 19; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Farrow, Mia and Allen, Woody, 1986-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 66)
      See also: Allen, Woody
    - Fasan, Onorina and Mario, 1986-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Faulkner-Saruk, Ann, 1978-1979; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Fecchi, Carlo, 1970 Sep. 5; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Feinstein, Bernice (Mrs. Martin), 1970 Aug. 17-27; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Feltsman, Vladimir and Anna, 1986-1989; 10 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Fenghi, Marte, 1982-1986; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Fennimore, Joseph, 1970 Apr. 20-27; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Fernand, Michael A., 1979 Jan. 6; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Ferrari, Giacomo, 1958 Oct. 14; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Feuermann, Sophie, 1974-1978; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Fidler, Beth, ca. 1988 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Field, Samson R., 1975-1989; 8 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Fierro, Arthur M., 1974-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Figaro, 1938 Jul. 6; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 68)
      Typed letter (copy) from Vladimir Horowitz
    - Film Society of Lincoln Center
      See: D'Arc, Karen
    - Finckel, David, 1988 Apr.-May; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Findlay, David A., 1989 Nov. 6; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Fine, Jessica, 1989 Oct. 5; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Fink, Peter and Monique, 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Fiorillo, Alexander, Jr., 1960 May 13-25; 7 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
      4 enclosures
    - Firkusny, Rudolf, 1988-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - First National City Bank, 1976 June 22; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Fiscella, Autumn, 1979-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Fischer, Albert E., 1965-1989; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Fisher, Avery, 1978-1989; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Fitz Patrick, Teresa, 1965 May 17-27; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Fitz Gerald, Paul
      See: Arndt-Condò, Erich
    - Flatt, Adrian E., M.D., 1976 Sep. 30; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Fleischmann, Ernest, 1977-1978; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz reply and 2 enclosures.
      See also: Los Angeles Philharmonic Association
    - Floriani, Virgilio and Loredana, 1989 Nov. 6; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Flug, Elaine A., ca. 1989 Nov. 28; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Foerster, Claudio E. von, 1970-1979; 51 items. (Box 5, Folder 70)
      Includes 8 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 14 enclosures
    - Fogel, Henry S.
      See: Chicago Symphony Orchestra
    - Foggin, Myers, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 71)
      See also: Royal Philharmonic Society
    - Fonda Fournier, Jean, 1976-1989; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fontaine, Stella
      See: Bagrit, Stella
    - Forman, Roy E., 1977-1978; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1971 June 30; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fossati-Bellani, Anna, [1989] Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Foster, Sidney, 1965-1976; 6 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fourquez, R., ca. 1978 Jul. 17; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fox, Donnette, 1989 Jan. 9-23; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Foyle, Christina, 1983 Sep. 5-21; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Fracchia, Piero
      See: Casa di Riposo per Musicisti
    - Francis, George, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Frank, Claude
      See: Kallir, Lilian
    - Frank, John Alfred, M.D., 1966 Nov.-Dec.; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Frank E. Campbell
      See: VIII. MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS. Items pertaining to Vladimir Horowitz's death and funeral
    - Franzin, Dino, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Freccia, Massimo and Nena, 1953-1965; 4 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Freches, José, 1983 Sep. 7; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Frédéric Chopinslichting Nederland, 1988-1991; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Freddi, Marina Chaliapine, 1989 Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Freese, Arthur S., 1979 Mar.-Apr.; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Freundlich, Irwin, 1965 June 16-30; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Friedberg, Annie, 1945 Oct. 30; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Friedberg, Carl, 1946 Mar.; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Friends of Animals, Inc., 1979-1980; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Frigerio, Sandra, 1991 May 12; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 72)
      2 photographs enclosed (photocopies) - originals with III. PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Froenke, Susan
      See: Maysles, Albert
    - Frolkin, Viktor Aleksandrovich, 1978 Mar. 14; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Fromer, Leon and Gina, 1965 June 1; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Frost, Tom and Lynn, 1967-1989; 30 items. (Box 5, Folder 73)
      Includes 6 Vladimir Horowitz replies and enclosure.
      See also: I.B. CBS Records Records - publicity
    - Frusciante, John A., 1967 Feb.-May; 7 items. (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Funayama, Nobuko, 1983 Feb.-Mar.; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Furman, Anne L. (Mrs. Saul), 1965 May 22; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - G. Henle Verlag, 1986 Mar.-May; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - G. Schirmer, Inc., 1967 Apr. 7-28; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Gagliardi, Lina B., 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Gaines, Samuel Richards, 1941 Apr. 20; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Gale, Eugenia, 1978-1989; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Gallaz, L., 1973 Jan. 3; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Ganz, Rudolph, 1967 Apr.-May; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Garbousovas, Raya, 1965-1968; 5 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
      Includs 2 Vladimir Horowitz replies
    - Gardiner, Robert, 1978 Oct.-Nov.; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Garfinkel, Barbara (Mrs. Burton), 1973-1977; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Garfinkel, Steven and Jodie, 1977-1988; 8 items. (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Garofalo, Marcello, 1972 Mar. 1; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Gastel, Ida, 1989 Nov. 9; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Gately, Thomas A., 1965 May 10-24; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Gavazzini, Gianandrea, 1967 July 9; 1 item. (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Gavoty, Bernard, 1966-1972; 34 items. (Box 5, Folder 77)
      Includes 7 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 3 enclosures.
      See also: I.B. CBS Records; and Paris - concert possibilites
    - Gavronsky, Mr.
      See: Weill, Erna
    - Gelb, Arthur and Barbara, ca. 1988 Oct. 1; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Gelb, Peter and Donna, 1976-1991; 48 items. (Box 6, Folder 79-80)
      Includes 3 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 53 enclosures.
      See also: CAMI Video; Carnegie Hall Corporation; Chukoron-sha, Inc.; Clavier; Columbia Artists Management Inc.; Concertgebouw; Funayama, Nobuko; Gladney, Norman; Hörzu; Olympic Gala; and Onkan
    - Gelfand, Yacov, 1988 Mar. 28; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Geemert, Monique G. van, n.d.; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - General Telephone & Electronics Corporation, 1969 Feb. 6; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 81)
      See also: Joe Wolhandler Associates, Inc.
    - Georgi, Walter, 1988 May 22; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Gerard, Edmund Bert, 1970 June-July; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
      See also: National Academy of Television Arts and Sciences
    - Gerbi, Giuliano, 1965 May 14; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Gerhart, Charles, 1986-1988; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Gershovskii, E.
      See: Dom Musei P.I. Chaikovskogo v Klinu
    - Gershunoff, Maxim and Van Dyke, Leon, ca. 1977 Nov. 3; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 81)
      See also: Hirshbein, Omus
    - Gerstman, Court C. and Mira, ca. 1965 May; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde in Wien (Box 6, Folder 81)
      See also: Angyan, Thomas
    - Gevorkian, Ara and Tsoline, 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Ghiringhelli, ?, 1965 Mar.-May; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Gilbert, Ernest, 1968 Oct.-Nov.; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Gilbert, Herschel Burke, 1976 May 3-13; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Gilels, Emil, 1956-1986; 13 items. (Box 6, Folder 83)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz reply and enclosure.
      See also: Staierskii?, P.S.
      Also includes Autograph letter signed from a student of Gilels Irina S-?) to Vladimir Horowitz.
    - Gimma, Joseph and Licia Albanese, 1965-1989; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 84)
      See also: Albanese, Licia
    - Ginder, Jean Dalrymple (Mrs. Philip DeWitt)
      See: Dalrymple, Jean
    - Gingerich, John, 1979 June 2-25; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 84)
      See also: Freese, Arthur S.; and Shaw Concerts
    - Ginori, Marchese Cristine, 1989 Nov. 11; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Giornale
      See: Mezzetti, Fernando
    - Gitterman, Joe, Joanna, Victoria, Tom, and Paul, ca. 1986 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Gladney, Norman, 1983 Feb.-Mar.; 6 items. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Glancy, Kenneth, 1965-1978; 8 items. (Box 6, Folder 84)
      Includes 4 Vladimir Horowitz replies.
      See also: BBC; CBS Records; and RCA
    - Glasser, Jane, 1989 Oct. 18; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Glick, Audrey V., ca. 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Glinka Central State Museum of Musical Culture, 1986 Apr. 25; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Glotz, Michel, 1966-1971; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 84)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz response and enclosure.
      See also: Murayama, Michi
    - Goberman, John, 1978 Sep. 13; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Gockel, Meinolf, 1987 June 12; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Godowsky, Dagmar, 1965-1966; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Godowsky, Leopold, 1965 Apr.-Jun.; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldberg, Albert, 1989 Nov. 14; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldberg, Barry, 1989-1990; 2 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldberg, Bernard, 1965 Mar. 18; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldenberg, Susan, 1972 Mar.-May; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Gol'denveizer, Elena Ivanovna, 1986 Apr. 20; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
      2 enlcosures
    - Gol'dshetin, Mikhail
      See: Goldstein, Michael
    - Goldstein, Gladys (Mrs. Sidney S.), n.d.; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldstein, Maurie, ca. 1989 Nov. 11; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goldstein, Michael, 1979 Sep.; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Golschmann, Odette and Vladimir ("Vova"), 1953-1965; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goode, David
      See: Good and Hutchinson
    - Good and Hutchinson (Karl, Robert, David, and Tom), 1979-1989; 5 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goodman, Sashe and Inna Rublova, 1965 May 11; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Goodrich, Peter G., 1981-1989; 7 items. (Box 6, Folder 85)
      See also: Steinway & Sons
    - Goodsell, Ginny and Frank, ca. 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1975-1978; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Gosconcert, 1989 Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Gottwald, Johannes, 1974 Feb. 21-28; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
      See also: Hesse, Otto and Inge
    - Gould, Morton, 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Gradova, Gitta
      See: Cottle, Gitta (Mrs. Maurice H.)
    - Graffman, Gary and Naomi, 1965-1990; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Graham, Martha
      See: Barber, Samuel
    - Graham, Robert, 1990 May 7-8; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Grand Street Settlement, 1988 Sep.-Oct.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Grant, Bess Myerson (Mrs. Arnold M.)
      See: Myerson, Bess
    - Grantley, Lord John and Lady Deirdre, 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Grassi, Paolo, 1972-1974; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Grausman, Philip, 1976-1989; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Gravina, Blanchine, 1933 June-Oct.; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 87)
      See also: Toscanini, Arturo
    - Green, Nancy, 1978 Sep. 6; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 87)
      Vladimir Horowitz reply and 2 enclosures
    - Gregorian, Vartan and Clare, 1987-1989; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Gregory, Alexis, ca. 1989 Nov. 29; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Gregory, Lydia and George ("Grisha"), 1933-1965; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Gregory, Paul, 1978-1988; 14 items. (Box 7, Folder 87)
      Includes 5 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 3 enclosures.
      See also: Shaw Concerts
    - Greidanus, Dineke and Gerhard, 1988 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Greiner, Alexander W. (Sasha), 1942-1957; 16 items. (Box 7, Folder 88)
      See also: Hofmann, Josef; Steinway & Sons; and VI.C. Steinway
    - Grève, Albert Michael, 1974 Oct.-Nov.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Gribanov, Mikhail, 1989 Nov. 10; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Griffin, Mary A., 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Griner, Jane, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Griner, Julia, ca. 1988 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Gross, Katharine, 1966 May 9; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Gross, Olga, 1979 July-Sep.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Grossman, Herb and Anne Chotzinoff ("Cookie"), 1988 Dec. 21-22; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Grottolo, Vera Benedicenti, 1989 Nov. 9; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Grove's Dictionary of Music & Musicians, 1972 Dec. 7; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Gruson, Sydney, 1976 June 2; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Guarneri, Sandro, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Guarneri Quartet
      See: Soyer, David
    - Guehenno, Jean-Marie, 1985 Jan. 2; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Günther, Walther, 1965 May 19; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Guerrant?, Elizabeth, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Guiding Eyes for the Blind, Inc., 1979-1990; 10 items. (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Includes Vladimir Horowitz reply and 4 enclosures
    - Guiton, Ellie Rogers, 1989 Dec. 5; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Gunn, J.F., 1989 Nov. 6; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Guroff, Gregory and Kathie, 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
      See also: Khazanovskii, Petya and Inna
    - Guroff, Sarah, 1989 Nov. 13; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Gurtman and Murtha Associates, Inc.
      See: Gelb, Peter
    - H.J. Behrman & Company, ca. 1986 Dec. 25; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Haas, Karl, 1979 June 29; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Haefele, Carol, 1965 June 1; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Haimowitz, Leonore, 1975 May 19-22; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Halim, Eduardus S. and Judy, 1988-1989; 9 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Hall, Bob, ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Halsted, Anna Roosevelt (Mrs. James A.)
      See: Roosevelt, Anna
    - Hamburg (Präsident des Senats der Freien und Hansestadt Hamburg), 1986-1987; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Hamburger Bach-Gesellschaft e.V., 1987 Jun. 11-19; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Hamilton, Rebecca Stickney, 1965 Dec. 9; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Hanes, Ralph
      See: Shaw, Harold
    - Hari, Kenneth, 1970-1988; 7 items. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Harlech, Pamela, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Harlem Hospital Center Auxiliary, Inc., ca. 1989 Nov.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Harold Clurman Theatre, 1980 May 22; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Harris, Robert, ca. 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Harrison, Jay S., 1965 Mar.-May; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Hart, Kitty Carlisle
      See: Carlisle, Kitty
    - Hartman, Arthur A. and Donna, [1986]-1989; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 92)
      2 enclosures.
      See also: United States. Embassy (Moscow)
    - Harvey Prize Fund, 1989 Mar.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Haskell, Jacqueline, ca. 1978 Sep. 25; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Hattauer, Charles, 1965-1966; 4 items. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - [Hausseman], Ida, 1983 Apr. 18; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Hay, A., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Hayes, Patrick, 1967-1981; 15 items. (Box 7, Folder 93)
      See also: Washington Performing Arts Society
    - Hazanovsky, Peter and Kirill, 1989 Nov. 8; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Hazard, John and Sue, 1981 Oct. 3; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Heath, Edward, 1982 Sep. 7; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Hecker, Tatiana, 1974 Nov. 19-26; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Hedley, Arthur, 1963-[1965?]; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Heidt, 1989 Nov. 7; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Heifetz, Jascha and Florence, 1933-1988; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Heifetz, Jay, ca. 1989 Nov. 21; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Heliotes, Steven, 1977-1988; 8 items. (Box 7, Folder 94)
      Includes 2 Vladimir Horowitz replies and an enclosure
    - Hemberger, Justine and Robert, ca. 1965 May 15; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 95)
      Addressed to Walter Toscanini
    - Henderson, Jack, 1951 Oct. 8; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Henderson, Ruth and Skitch, 1986-1989; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
      See also: New York Pops
    - Hendl, Walter, 1966-1986; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Henle, G., 1973 Mar.-Oct.; 8 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
      Includes 3 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 4 enclosures.
      See also: G. Henle Verlag
    - Henneking, Antje, 1991 Aug. 23; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
      2 business cards laid in
    - Hensel, Bruckmann & Lorbacher, Inc., 1975 Aug. 24; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Hensler, Guenter and Maren, 1988-1990; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herbst, Ray, 1989 Feb. 7-15; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herder, Ronald
      See: G. Schirmer, Inc.
    - Hermann, Jane, 1986-1988; 6 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herz, Maria, 1938 July 11; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herzeca, Josette D. (Mrs. Lincloln J.), 1989 Mar.-May; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herzer, Clifford, 1965-1988; 11 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Herzfeld, Wolfgang and J. Cline, ca. 1989 Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M., Rev., C.S.C., 1982 Feb.-Mar.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Hesse, Otto and Inge, 1974 Dec. 1; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 95)
      See also: Gottwald, Johannes
    - High Fidelity Magazine, 1973 Feb. 23; 3 items. (Box 132)
      Caine Alder's discography and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz's memorandum with additions and corrections to the discography laid in - oversize
    - Hillyer, Kazuko (Mrs. Raphael), 1966-1969; 6 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hilton, Jeanne, 1965 May 24; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hindell, Leonard, 1978 Jan. 17; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hirn, Wolfgang, 1988 Nov. 1; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hirsch, Georges-François, 1985-1989; 5 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hirschberg, Peter and Elfi, 1987 May; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hirshbein, Omus, 1980 Nov. 10; 3 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
      2 enclosures, including typed letter from Vladimir Horowitz to Maxim Gershunoff
    - Hirshfield, Lucile K., ca. 1989 Nov. 7; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hirshman, Henriette (Genia), 1953-1965; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Hochschule für Musik und Darstellende Kunst (Wien), 1987 Jun. 29; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hochstein, David Jay, 1985 Dec.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hodes, Rosalee and Arthur, ca. 1988 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hörzu, 1986 Dec. 18; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hofmann, J. Anton, 1967 Feb. 6; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hofmann, Josef, 1940 Feb. 2; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Hogg, Ima
    - Holland, Bill and Mary Jo, Peter, and Russell, 1987 Sep. 30; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Holm, Hans Henrik, 1968 Sep.-Oct.; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Holschneider, Andreas, 1986-1991; 19 items. (Box 7, Folder 98)
      Includes 4 Vladimir Horowitz replies and 5 enclosures.
    - Holt, Harold and Olive, 1938-1951; 2 items. (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Holt, Hilda, 1978 Jan. 5; 1 item. (Box 7, Folder 99)